so we're a week of the moon what nobody
has ever done before and that's turn one
of these hundred dollars into a million
dollars absolutely everything has been
documented here to China we're already
eight weeks into the series where I'm
documenting it on my YouTube Instagram
telegram Discord so not only do you guys
learn from my mistakes but can also copy
the trades that I am taking and see
exactly what my strategy is about we
started seven weeks ago in the first
attempt we obviously blew it but now
last week we turned forty six thousand
dollars to eighty thousand dollars this
week we're gonna try and turn those
eighty thousand dollars to a hundred
sixty thousand dollars I know it sounds
crazy but we're already two months into
this challenge so let's see what this
week's takes us and let the series begin
[Music]
all right what's up guys so it is Sunday
market open so let me show you guys the
pairs that we're going to be trading
this week because
what we got to turn these 80k or
technically 78 000 into 160 by the end
of this week
I was doing the math and the lots that
we got to start using and we're probably
already hitting the 80 90 lots for you
know if you throw 100 I'd say no you're
uh
big boy big boy so let me show you guys
the account so right here we are
currently at 78 000 on the account and
it's kind of crazy how we've literally
turned the hundred dollars into this and
now this week the goal is to obviously
turn it into 160 which is going to be
double that so last week if you guys saw
last week's video we only took one trade
and one trade took us from 20 that no it
was from forty thousand to the 78 000
that we are now if you haven't seen that
video make sure you guys go last week so
let's break down the top three your top
four pairs that I'm going to be trading
this week so let me show you guys so
let's start off with my number one pair
for the week which is going to be AUD
USD so we have the wiggly bearish daily
bearish and then the four hour time
frame is bullet so obviously this means
that the majority of the markets are
headed to the downside so the most
logical thing to do on this trade would
be to then buy as you guys can see we
have two time frames down one time frame
up the one time frame that is up does
not outweigh these two time frames that
the market is going down so you guys can
see here this is the strong area of
interest you have one rejection one
above one rejection one above and
whenever under we are selling so as of
right now I've placed this line right
here because I want price to come back
into this area to then retest to go to
the downside as you guys can see we have
broken through that zone already because
the market is moving very fast like the
Market's been open probably for a couple
of hours and we've already broken
through the Zone I drew this up probably
earlier today while the market had just
opened at five o'clock it's around
midnight right now on Sunday so we were
looking for price to pull back into this
area right here reject and then sell so
for right now we are no longer
interested in this trade because it has
broken above the area of interest you
can see whenever we are above this area
we are buying so I'm going to simply be
waiting for price to now come do this
break this area retest under round
psychological 64
000 and then I will be interested in a
trade so my bias Remains the Same I just
have to wait for the break under the
area of interest to them so
next AUD cat so AUD cat is very similar
to AUD USD you have a very clean left
head right shoulder at a strong area of
Interest this right here is your head
and shoulders and right now we're coming
back up to create that right shoulder
once again at a strong area of interest
and very similar to AUD USD the weekly
time frame on this is bearish daily time
frame is bearish as well and then the
four hour let's check the four hour the
four hour is bearish so this is the
lower high point right here so this
would be the lower high and then this
would be the lower low at that structure
point right there as you can see we
haven't broken above or under either of
those two structure points meaning that
the four hour time frame is bearish as
well so this right here gives us an even
more clear indication that this Market
is going to start heading to the
downside because we have all three time
frames in sync so the most logical thing
to do is to look for a cell so that's
exactly what we're going to do right now
and that is why I placed this area of
Interest right here because whenever we
are under we're selling whenever we're
under we're selling whenever we're above
we're buying whenever we're above we're
buying and as you can tell right here
we're under so we're going to then sell
so I'm going to simply be waiting for a
rejection from this area it can be
anything around a bearish engulfing
Candlestick then a wig pullback but I am
ready to take this trade very very very
soon I think this can even happen
tonight during London but this is my
second number one pair for the week
which actually it's going to move to my
top one because this AUD USD trade is no
longer as high of a probability trade as
AUD cash so I'm going to be looking to
enter this trade very soon now during
London next we have AUD JPY so these are
the two trades that we took I think it
was on week three or week four of the
challenge which we lost these trades
right here as you can see all the trades
that I take I always in the history of
the market and this week on this trade I
have a very simple analysis keep it very
simple and is I'm just going to wait for
the market we're on the daily time frame
right now you guys can tell right here
we're on the daily time frame I'm just
gonna wait for this Market to do two
things
either break out to the upside I wait
for the retest to then buy or wait for
the breakout to the downside wait for
the retest and then sell as you can see
we've been accumulating at this area now
for almost two months and I don't want
to get stuck in this Zone whenever we
break under this is a very strong wall
respected area of Interest so that once
we break under will then sell so we'll
break read the cell or break reaches by
very simple and it is the exact same
thing that we're looking for on uh
nzdjpy but nzd JPY we want to take the
bias to the upside but doesn't really
matter as you can see right here we're
creating a very solid inverted Head and
Shoulders left head right shoulder so
what we need to do is for us to break
that neckline and then re-test the
keypad into the upside whenever we're
under the Zone we're selling whenever
we're above we're buying above above
buying Under selling so we're literally
just looking for the market to do what
we just did right here break retest buy
break retest buy but for now we're going
to keep our focus on one AUD CAD which
is looking very solid to give us an
entry very soon so I know that might be
information overload but we do this
every week with the students we lose
every week on Instagram telegram you
guys should know by now so let's check
in uh tomorrow in the morning because
it's gonna take a quick nap probably
have we have two hours two and a half
hours before London session starts
and I'm ready for water all right what
is up guys good morning so it's a later
morning than how I usually do the
updates but it is the official first
Monday morning of the week and we got
into the trade exactly as I explained a
little bit in drawdown but let me show
you guys how it's looking right now so
it is currently right now 11 20 in the
morning usually I update around 9 30 in
the morning but the market literally had
no movement so we got in on the AUD CAD
trade when price pulled back to the air
Adventures as I've been anticipating
price came back retested and now in the
daily perfectly rejecting this point
right here I love the four hour
rejection Candlestick I love how I had a
solid bearish engulfing confirming that
area and then most important most
importantly on the pullback from the 30
minute time frame it had that bearish
engulfing Evening Star formation right
there so I went pretty low risk I risked
about 15 on this trade uh it's the
beginning of the week that I want to go
too crazy so I'm going to add a position
once we do this right here once we kind
of you either break and retest this zone
right here let me just draw it out this
zone right here or once we break and
re-test
this zone right here just get that box
one second
so many things so
there you go once I break and retest
this zone right here I'll be potentially
adding another Trace so now we're
looking so far AUD USD pretty much broke
through that area of Interest so as of
right now I'm no longer interested in it
until we don't break and re-test under
nzd JPY still waiting for the breakout
to the upside we're going to keep
remaining patient on this one and then a
djpy pretty much same thing waiting for
the breakout so just to recap basically
how we're looking right now and we're
just gonna do a little quick
seven forget
yo trade update hey oh no
all right yeah we're good so we're here
with the boy joining right now yo so
trade update let me show you guys
exactly how the trade is looking so
we're up right now about 4 400 on the
trade so looking pretty solid right now
we're the boy Jordan we're gonna go eat
right now uh and then after that
probably hit the gym yo drop drop him
some wisdom bro just say some words yeah
some words of wisdom
um so the main thing and anything guys
is consistency so you guys are seeing
Alex for example on his 100 to 80k you
guys are seeing the consistency every
single day how he shows up even if he
doesn't trick or trade he shows up and
me myself as well I'm on a 12-week
consecutive winning streak and it's
literally the consistency that gets you
there it doesn't matter what you're
going through like for example if you
haven't seen my store you should check
it out on Instagram it'll definitely
motivate you if you're like in a tough
spot or if you're going through
something but like I said it's a
consistency in the tough spots that will
get you to the to the better spots
some more of the story
all right market update so it is
currently 9 22 at night you guys can see
where I currently have about seven
thousand dollars on the trade well seven
thousand dollars right now trade is
looking very very precise but we're
about to enter London session you know
London session can go crazy in our favor
or against it so let me show you guys so
this is exactly what we are waiting for
on AUD card as you can tell we entered
up here earlier this morning perfectly
we entered pretty much little to no
drawbound we entered at the bearish
engulfing of that Candlestick so now I
love the fact of how we're doing what we
anticipated if I were to want to enter a
trade which was a retest of the zone to
then keep heading to the downside I
didn't add an entry just because we
weren't in the right session but now if
we do have a pullback into this area a
little bit more solid and then we reject
I will be adding an entry we just have
to make sure the momentum of London
session doesn't break through this Zone
and then kind of go back into our entry
and potentially put us into drawdown on
this trade so I don't like the fact of
how the daily time frame has closed one
second my computer's glitching I don't
like how this daily time frame has
closed above that Candlestick right
there I don't like how the wick has
Wicked above that point right there I
really don't like that but I do like how
my stop loss is above that Wick because
even if this daily Candlestick Wick
decides to go a little bit higher it'll
probably not break above this and it'll
create a higher Wick just like this one
in equal Wick to that length and an
eagle weight to that length we are still
good in the trade stop losses above and
it's still under the area of Interest so
the goal and the ideal thing for
tomorrow would be a bearish engulfing to
then break the zone to keep heading to
the downside so we're going to look for
a little pullback to add a trade if not
our next added entry will then be at
this area right here to then take the
trade to the downside AUD USD we are
still waiting for the same exact thing
waiting for price to break and read the
Zone in order for us to sell to the
downside nzd JPY we are waiting for this
time frame to break out to either side
still we haven't done that and same
thing with AUD JPY waiting for it to
break out so so far the only trade we
are in is looking very nice very
precisely in profit and uh yeah now
we're just gonna forget
all right what is up guys good morning
so it is currently nine well pretty much
10 in the morning I was just doing the
Instagram stories right now we're
training London last night we caught the
trade that I explained last night
perfectly to the tea we have officially
turned a hundred dollars into six
figures so let me show you guys the
trade and not how only I caught it but
how everybody on my Instagram everybody
on my Discord telegram everybody these
trades are out there publicly so this is
where you currently are on the account
we're currently up about thirty two
thousand dollars we are up at a hundred
and eleven thousand dollars in equity we
take the AUD CAD trade so this is
yesterday's trade that we were in drop
down went into profit and then we added
this position last night during London
session very clean very simple trade but
it is exactly what I explained we
explained earlier this week we're gonna
wait for price to come back into this
area to then sell and then last night
during London session or before London
session I explained that hey guys I'm
gonna be waiting for a pullback into
then this level to enter the trade would
you look at that we have a perfect
double top entry confirmation from
rejecting this area of interest and not
only do we have a double top but then we
have a bearish engulfing Candlestick
Evening Star formation confirming that
rejected and if you look at the time if
I just drag this all the way down here
that is at 3 30 in the morning which it
is London session but that's not only it
if we come here to the free telegram you
guys can see how in the free telegram I
sent it last night I sent it literally
at midnight and I said cough cough cough
take the trade I even sent a reminder at
1 20 in the morning this is what I sent
to the telegram people at 1 20 in the
morning
more blessings and more love I know a
lot of y'all hugging your pillow putting
slob all over zippers in and lick the
wounds out of the face you call it
zipper face
I'm out here going getting it and then I
literally tell him I'm like yo wake up
zipper faces it's 1 20 in the morning
the trade is about to play out and then
would you look at that but it's not only
that I sent this trade completely on
Sunday and you can see right there
perfect trade analysis for the cell
perfect trade analysis for the sale So
currently right now on this trade I am
very confident I'm just gonna keep
holding it if anything keeps scaling but
for now we're just going to set and
forget and let this trade do its thing
ad USD didn't make it to bring the
retails under and neither of these other
trades have broken above or under so
we're just going to keep our focuses on
the trade right now that is currently
making us the profits and that it is
looking very very solid and I mean like
this shows you guys how like I've
literally turned a hundred dollars into
six figures by just following my trading
plan I've been doing the same thing now
for two months obviously my goal was to
turn the 100 into the mill by now
obviously in the challenge I realized
that that's actually very difficult
that's not it's easier said than done
right so I'm about 900k away but I'm
just like a couple flips away I'd say
I'm about seven to eight good trades
away from turning this 100K into a mill
now because if I was able to turn 100
into 100K I can definitely turn 100K
into a ml so um it only gets easier from
here but this just shows you guys that
the consistency I'm here every single
day showing the Traders every single day
showing you guys every single day waking
up every single day and just doing my
routine every single day I haven't
traveled outside of my home during this
whole entire challenge because I want to
focus on this challenge I love traveling
I would love to you know be right now in
Cape Town I would love to be right now
in Dubai in Spain or New York right now
for fashion week I would love to be in
all those places you know just meeting
cool people because I'm able to do it
I'm a profitable Trader I have freedom
I'm young I can do all that stuff
but I want to show you guys that this is
possible first I feel like my duty as a
person that has come from nothing to be
able to be living in a neighborhood like
this to be able to have in cars like the
ones that I have is to be transparent
and show you guys that this is possible
so don't take this for granted what I'm
doing because nobody's gonna put this
type of dedication into this journey so
somebody else can replicate it and have
and have success with it as well so I'm
gonna keep going I'm going to make this
challenge possible and then after that I
would roll I'll you know I'll reload it
myself but in the meantime just get back
to work
and snacks before the gym
I'm gonna go get wait we gotta get the
sunlight in there you can see like the
bicep see the bicep more on the side no
I gotta hit one 60 this week and then
I'll be done for those so you're still
gonna make another 16. yeah
it's only Tuesday bro
all right trade update so it is
currently 10 30 at night so I was
supposed to update this a little bit
earlier but I was out on the road and I
anticipated this pullback to Perfection
did it come back to the Zone where I
wanted to so I can add a position in the
trade but nonetheless we're looking good
so let me show you right now where we
are on the account so right now we are
still in the both same trades and we're
at a hundred twenty thousand dollars
floating profit and honestly it feels
good to be back in these profits like I
haven't been in these seven profits I
think in almost like a month and a half
because obviously I've been scanning the
account from you know 100 bucks to where
it is now so now you know back to the 40
50k days it's been good so let me show
you guys what I meant today on the trade
right so AUD CAD we anticipated for the
daily time frame to then close very
bearish ideally I don't love the fact of
how it did not body close under this
point right here this daily Candlestick
never body close under which is not
great but I did expect for this Wick
pool back to come back and retest these
body structures here and is where I drew
out this black line so it retests those
body structures there and then on the
four hour time frame that retesting that
structure point would be retesting this
left shoulder in a way and this
structure Point here as well as you can
see price never came back all the way up
into that area so I was never able to
add a position into the trade but when
it retested that zone it was going to
also retest the one hour EMA so I was
going to look to add a position at this
point right here but we simply didn't
make it to that point by a couple of
fips but nonetheless the direction of
the market is still headed in our favor
so the next tray that I'm looking to
enter is going to be the break and then
retest of this zone right here so we can
continue skating the trade to the
downside AUD USD we are still waiting
for the same exact thing in order for us
to enter this trade which is going to be
a break and retest to them so nzd JPY we
are still waiting for a break and retest
to go to the upside and then AUD JPY
we're waiting for a break and retest
either side so we're into the trade
right now that's having clear momentum
that's why you want to enter a trade
that has all time frames in sync so so
far looking good and we are currently
floating about
forty four thousand dollars in profit
set and forget
all right trade update so it is
currently 10 18 in the morning so last
night's trade hit our take profit
perfectly I even sent my daily DJ Khaled
message to tell you guys close to trade
wake up zipper faces let me show you
right here you guys can see
130 000 right now on the account from
the hundred dollars it's crazy because
it's hitting me right we're officially
at the six figure mark this year we're
floating in profit like that but now
we're officially closed profit there so
let me show you guys so this is
currently where the uh the trade is
right now so I low key regret closing
where I close because I do believe this
has so much more downside potential but
I'll be adding an entry very very soon
if we do get the entry signal basically
price came down last night hit our take
profit area and I literally sent a
message in my free telegram you guys can
see here 6 40 in the morning
[Music]
zipper face
zipper face wake up gotta get this money
so now this trade has officially been
closed very solid trade setup I do
believe we are going to continue heading
to the downside though if we reject this
area of Interest right here on the lower
time frame which we technically already
are as you can see we're doing that as
we speak but I feel like the safer entry
is going to be once we break this area
and then retest it so then continue
heading to the downside that's going to
be the safer trade and it's what I'm
going to be expecting to do it is
currently Tuesday I mean no it's
Wednesday right yeah it's Wednesday
Wednesday
Wednesday 10 20 in the morning
but this challenge has been crazy
because I'm trading London and New York
at the same time so I don't know or
whatever so let me show you guys so next
trade that we got is going to be
AUD USD which AUD USD we have been
waiting for this breaking retest here
which you still haven't got in it just
waiting being patient on that the next
trade is going to be ANZ the nzd JPY
which is going to be the break I read
this of the Zone which it looks like
we're finally about to break out but we
still have about six hours left on this
daily Candlestick so once I did the
Candlestick closes then we will pretty
much wait for it to break and re-test
add JPY we are currently still stuck in
the same spot so our main focus will
remain here for now because this is the
one that's giving us the majority of the
profits and if we body close under this
right here that means we're body closing
under the neckline of The Head and
Shoulders which is going to give this
humongous downside potential so we're
gonna for now set and forget
and yeah see where this trade takes us
so we're gonna probably not take any
trades for the rest of the day I Think
We're not gonna get an entry signal and
we're just gonna enjoy the rest of our
day and then check back in tonight
during the London session so check it
out all right trade update it's
currently 11 30 at night I feel like I
do the updates the same time but at Am
Pm does that make anything whatever the
point is that
let me just show you it's still exactly
the same we haven't taken any other
trades on the account right now the
trade where we pulled out was perfect
let me show you so right here you can
tell that we got out at our take profit
area I was low-key regretting pulling
out earlier this morning because there
was still a lot more profit left on the
table but trade obviously bounced back
from that area I don't really like how
the daily rejected this zone right here
because I would have loved if the daily
Candlestick would have body closed under
that zone we didn't body glued on this
and I were rejecting but I do like how
we are pulling back right now right
before London session so now what I'm
going to expect is for in any rejections
from this zone right here pretty much
how we've done it in the past and I'm
going to be waiting for a clean entry
signal which you kind of already had it
but we got to see if now in the lower
time frame you could get another bearish
engulfing from this area where it can
potentially give us a head and shoulders
at this area of Interest right here and
then if not I'm gonna simply be waiting
for the trade once it does exactly what
I've been anticipating which is pretty
much great this area retest it to keep
heading to the downside AUD USD we
haven't broken under the area in order
for me to sell no trade very simple
nzdjpy we have broken above the area and
now it looks like we're going to be
retesting this Zone which is very solid
not as strong as of a break as I've been
anticipating so I have to be pretty much
on the lookout but I do like how it's
kind of retesting this zone right here
I'm going to be on the lookout to see if
we can get a clean entry signal at this
area and then last but not least is AUD
JPY which we've managed to have it push
to the upside but not break through this
resistance level so I'm going to put my
focus right now on nzd JPY for some
trades long during London session and
then AUD CAD for some shorts during
London session as well so check back up
with you guys tomorrow in the morning if
I don't take anything tonight in London
so once again 11 30. P.M
all right what's up guys so trade update
I actually haven't done a trade update
because I completely forgot was trading
London last night and then basically the
uh the camera is not here so I just
completely forgot but trade up there
right now on the trade let me show you
guys how it's looking so this is the
trade to currently explained exactly as
I explained that you guys can see how
last night I was basically anticipating
for trade to have a rejection from that
right shoulder right there and we had
that entry beautiful everybody on
Instagram caught it everywhere this
trade happened to Perfection we had the
bearish engulfing Candlestick then we
had the push to pull back I had my stop
loss strategically placed above the wick
in that zone this is how we are
currently looking on the account we're
up about nine thousand dollars went
relatively low risk on this trade if
this trade ends up being able to fulfill
all the way to the downside we might be
able to hit our goal of 160 for the week
um but yeah looking pretty solid the
fact that we still have this very strong
support level holding price up it's a
little bit of a turn off I really don't
like that but I'm it is what it is you
just have to
forget until the trade goes so if it
does break and retest this Zone I will
be adding in position very very soon so
let them sounded if it from here needs
20 000 more to go
so trade update it is currently one
o'clock in the morning forgot to kind of
update earlier this morning but the
trade came back took us how to break
even and I kind of missed another trade
so let me show you guys exactly what I
mean like sucks because I don't think
we're gonna be able to hit our goal like
I'm trading London right now one in the
morning trying to see if we can get
those last 30k to reach our goal but
let's see let me show you guys we
currently are in your account 131 000 so
we will probably have about 10 000 total
on the trade but we are rejecting very
very strong this zone right here this is
why I want to sell once we break your
retest under the zone so we have
actually been struggling to break
through this and that's exactly where we
had the rejection from to come back up
now I just wanted to show you guys that
if I would have not closed that break
even would have pretty much hit our stop
loss so right now the account is looking
I mean this trade is looking okay like
maybe we can add a sell here potentially
for London session
um I am going to keep on the lookout
though I'm not a hundred percent there I
want you get a nice bearish engulfing
here if not my efforts will come back
and be on nzd JPY if you guys can tell
this is what we explained yesterday we
explained I was looking for the break
and retest to take the trade up we had
the beautiful break beautiful retest and
we're going up so uh kind of missed it
in a way but I do think we can pull back
again next week and enter it it is
currently right now
September 15th one o'clock in the
morning so it's Friday one in the
morning so we have a couple hours left
in the market nothing else in the
Market's really interesting me this
never broke and retested under to them
so so I'm gonna see if we can
potentially get some sales here if not
we'll just wait for this one next week
all right what's up guys so not gonna
lie I woke up a little bit late it is
currently right now 12 o'clock in the
morning well in the afternoon because
honestly trading the London session
really got to me and it kind of played
out in my way I did miss the trade that
I was anticipating last night but it is
what it is I don't really care about it
because I have a really high expectation
for what the market is going to do next
week so it is what it is I didn't hit my
target for the week but let me show you
guys what the market is lining up for
next week I think it is very very solid
and I think next week now we know we're
going to reach our goal but I think
we're going to Circle pass it
so this is AUD USD you guys can see how
last night we were anticipating for
price to either break and retest to then
head to the downside or come back into
this area how it did and then have our
rejection from here and that's exactly
what we did so I did not take the trade
I was totally knocked out last night if
you guys can see we have the left head
and then pretty much the right shoulder
right here with the bearish engulfing
but look at the time that that Trader is
lining up 3 45 in the morning yeah I'm
sorry I'm human last night I completely
fell asleep this would have been the
entry that I would have taken stop loss
above we would be in decent profit I
don't know if it would have been enough
to get our profits for the week but what
I do like is that it is respecting this
zone so this gives me high indication
that next week we're going to have a
very very solid move on this trade you
guys can tell we are currently still
rejecting it but there's not much time
left in the market it's currently Friday
12 o'clock in the afternoon so there's
not much momentum that the market can
still have with pretty much four hours
left in the market before it closes so
for now I'm going to remain with the
same bias and that is I'm going to only
sell at the break and retest of this
Zone next week you can tell we're very
very strongly supporting above it and
we've been pretty much accumulating in
this area and this is what I was
explaining to the people on my Instagram
we've been accumulating at this area for
pretty much
one two three four five six seven eight
days so for the last eight days it's
accumulating you guys know once price
accumulates it's gonna do something
right it's gonna accumulate and then
blow up or accumulate and then blow down
but after us identifying that we have
all these three time frames bearish we
have a high indication that this
accumulation is going to keep going to
the downside because we know where the
trio trend of the market is so this is
why I have a very high expectation of
this coin to the downside and then next
we have nzb JPY which we basically
technically missed but it came back to
give us another entry but same thing as
AED USD I strongly think this trade is
going to give us a solid solid setup for
next week but before that let me show
you guys where the account is right now
you guys can see the account is at 131
000 so we didn't hit our goal by 29 000
for the week
but this pair right here we've been
we've been anticipating all week for it
to break out so we can pretty much leave
all of this accumulation right here if
you notice we've been accumulating for
almost 48 days in this zone so now we're
finally having the break out of that
zone retesting and now it's going to
keep heading to the upside and it's a
very perfect example compared to AUD CAD
because we're having the accumulation
here but to head to the downside that's
where the majority of the trend is and
then here we're going to have the
accumulation and break up to the upside
because that is where the majority of
the trend is the weekly time frame is
bullish the daily timeframe is bullish
and the four hour time frame is bullet
so that's why the accumulation is going
to indicate to us that we're going to
head to the upside so this trade right
here last night I said the only way I
would take it is if it pulls back look
at that perfect pullback but I can only
take it next week so very very solid
trade setups next week I think this
might be my number one and this be my my
might be my number two pair for next
week so I'm very very excited for next
week so obviously we didn't hit our goal
for the week which was 160 000 which
obviously sucks you know we want to hit
our goal because because my goal is
every single week to double up from the
original starting balance so I was
supposed to be at 160 this week but it's
okay because I feel like the markets all
of this week they've been setting up to
give me a high probability setup for
next week meaning that the fact that it
caught profitable trades this week and I
made money in the account is a huge plus
because I would strongly strongly do
believe that the pairs have been setting
up all of this week to have the big move
next week so I do believe next week we
can have not only solid moves but we can
also have more profits than we were
initially supposed to have because of
these pairs loading up all week so I'm
very excited
um you know obviously this week the
London session did take a toll on me it
was very frustrating it was very tiring
but did pay off for the time that I did
do it I'm going to organize my sleep
schedule a little bit better uh the last
thing that I did learn this week was get
some rest you know we've been doing this
now for two months so I've been learning
a lot as myself I've been learning more
more from the markets I'm always a
student of the markets and I'm getting
closer to the goal I'm almost there and
I'm excited I'm excited for what's going
to happen next week so make sure you
guys tune in to week nine all right so
let's have a recap of how this week went
so we started off Monday morning with
AUD card where we entered the trade you
guys saw that we were in a little bit of
drop down but the trade went into profit
shortly after that right the trade went
into profit we were anticipating for
price to not only continue going down
but then have a pullback with the trade
that is where we entered the second
position on the AED Academy that gave us
good amount of profit which didn't get
us to our goal of 160 for the week but
we ended up closing at the take profit
Zone with that strong area of interest
that AUD CAD keeps on rejecting from and
that's where we closed at about a
hundred thirty thousand dollars in
profit then that's where we waited for
price and have the pullback go to the
next area of interest and then there we
added the next position which is going
to give us the last profits of our trade
where it's going to give us our goal of
160 for the lead but obviously price
didn't do that what if it's a profit we
went back into that strong supports
level and then we rejected from it and
you know got all right I'll break even
didn't make any money and we didn't hit
our goal of 160 for the week but this is
a perfect week to show you guys how less
is more just like the last week before
because you don't need to take a bunch
of Trades you only trade one pair for
this week and we're taking the same
exact trade same exact strategy and I do
this every single week you guys have
been following along now for two months
in this journey you guys are not only
seeing how I'm doing it but how
thousands of my students are doing that
with the set and forget strategy that
allows any of them to make a thousand to
a thousand five hundred dollars a week
as a beginner using my set and forget
strategy you want to know more about
what the center forget is and like
actually like what does it mean I have a
link in the description below that
defines what the center forget means the
full video that explains how a center
figure Works how I came up with it and
how those Traders use it to make numbers
like a thousand a week two thousand even
three thousand dollars a week using my
beginner certificate strategy so if you
guys want to know more about that click
the link in the description below and I
will see you guys next week for the
series because now we're gonna try to
take this for 130 to about quarter Mill
300K we're almost at the million dollar
ago so see you guys next week